We have breaking news. It happened
just a few moments ago apparently.
We have very little information available.
We have, I understand,
an eyewitness on the phone right now.
Rog.
In the middle of the Plaza at 8:52.
With limited information at this point,
we don't know
about injuries in the building...
What the hell happened?
A bomb.
I think.
So sad.
- There was a loud sound...
- Rog, I got to...
I can only describe it as, it sounded
like a missile, not an airplane.
Then there was a loud explosion and...
Wanna go higher?
So, the Red Sox
with two down on a base hit
- first time through the order?
- Third.
Third?
- What inning is this?
- Fifth.
Oh, boy.
Your hands are...
Your hands are... disgusting.
I et me do it.
Disgusting?
Wow.
Just breathe.
He pops that one up down the line.
That's ducking in! It falls in!
- What's the inning of that game?
- Third.
Let's go!
Come on, Henry!
You got it, you got it!
Dive, dive, dive!
Out!
Hey, how do you say "dive"?
- Dive?
- It's a tough one.
Come on.
- Go Marcus!
- Here we go. Nice little hit. Here we go.
Ball!
That's okay. Good eye, good eye!
Alright, Marcus.
Wait for your pitch, buddy.
This damage with two oults...
Shit.
Strike onel
it's alright.
Goddamn thing.
Strike two!
Come on. Let's go.
Alright, folks. That's the game.
Why don't we all head to our cars.
- Okay, let's go.
- Molly!
- What was that?
- I don't know.
- I don't know what that was.
- I'm gonna take the kids home, okay?
Okay, yeah. My truck's up on main street.
Okay. Alright, everybody in. Let's go.
I'll go with dad.
Okay. Straight home. Lee?
- Hey. You alright?
- Yeah, good.
Your brother say anything
going on at the base?
Not that I know of.
He just called. Let me call him back.
Alright. Yeah, let me know.
My truck's up there.
Don't worry.
Wait here.
Ronnie, what do we got?
We got units headed out there now,
ems and fire.
- Whereabouts?
- I think out by Walker's farm.
What's wrong?
It's okay, honey. It's okay, honey bunny.
It's okay, baby. It's okay.
Mom? Yeah.
What is happening?
Oh, my god!
It's okay. It's okay. We're okay.
- That's dad. That's dad!
- Where, where, where?
Mom. Mom!
Oh, my god!
- You're okay, baby.
- I'm okay.
It's okay, honey. It's okay.
I'm okay.
We were on main street and... I don't...
Are you there?
Mom?
Our father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Give us this day our daily...
It's okay.
It's dad!
Down. Get down.
Let's go.
Wait here.
I'm going back in...
Stay here.
Run!
Baby, please.
No. Please.
It's okay, honey. It's okay.
It's okay.
Go.
Jump.
You can't stay.
I don't know why you came
all the way up here, but you can't stay.
Up?
There's not enough food... water.
There's not enough anything.
How do you know we traveled up?
There's nothing I can do.
You won't survive.
Show me your face.
I can't help you.
Please, I can't help you.
Emmett?
Please.
Breathe, baby.
How does it work?
There's three feet of concrete.
They'd have to be right above us to hear.
What is it? Some kind of...
Some kind of feedback from the microphone?
It just works. I don't know.
Just never seen one dead before.
How is he?
He's...
Well, it didn't reach the bone.
But that wrap won't last.
I'm sorry.
- For what?
- The boys.
- I assume...
- That day.
And Nora?
Eleven weeks ago.
She was sick.
Held out as long as we could in the house.
But the pain just...
It was when she started screaming...
We had to come here.
That was smart.
It wasn't enough.
Can I ask you a question?
When you saw the flame...
Night after night...
Did you know it was him?
Yes.
And did you ever think to come for us?
No.
The people that are left...
What they've become...
You don't know, do you?
Well, I do.
They're not a kind of people worth saving.
What is it?
- What is it?
- Music!
- It's...
- "Beyond the sea."
- Have you heard this?
- Yes.
No. Dad would've heard this.
It's the same song. It's been playing
over and over the last four months.
You're lying!
My dad used the radio every day!
- What's she saying?
- She thinks he would've heard it.
Who?
Lee.
It's the valley.
It's the valley. I tried the radio
from our house too,
but we never heard anything
until we got up here.
Your dad was never gonna make it work.
You're nothing
you're nothing like
you're nothing like him!
Does this mean that there are more people?
- I don't know, baby. I don't.
- No!
There's nothing left.
I told you, there is nothing left.
I want you gone tomorrow.
It's not a song.
On the radio.
Beyond the sea...
Beyond the sea... right?
It's not a song...
It's a signal.
They're telling us where to look.
I looked up the radio station.
Where the song is coming from.
It's an island!
I can follow the train tracks...
It's not even one day.
Then I can find a boat.
You can't do this.
If I can find the song.
Where it's coming from...
I can use this...
To change this...
Into this!
Mom,
mom, will
mom, will never...
Mom, will never... let you go.
I can
I can save
I can save them.
I can
I can save
I can save us.
I'll tell her.
Mom...
Please don't do this!
I need to try.
Why?
Because dad would.
And look what happened to him.
You have to find her for me.
She's gone to get help, and I need you to
go and find her and bring her back to me.
- Alright, listen to me.
- Please, Emmett, I'm begging you.
- Evelyn...
- I'm begging you. We were friends.
Emmett, please.
Lee is gone.
Now he's gone.
It's a shame.
Because if he were here...
He'd look you right in the eye,
and he'd tell you
that his little girl is absolutely
the kind of person worth saving.
So please go find her...
And bring her back to me.
Gol
Alright, listen to me.
We stay here until they're gone,
and then we go.
You understand?
She can't hear.
You can't hear.
Shit!
I'm taking you home.
We'll wait here until they're gone.
Goddamn it!
Fnunciate...
Fnunciate... remember?
I'm
taking you... back.
Hey.
They heard... the shot.
Okay?
Nol!
You can't do this.
Help me.
Enough, please. Enough.
I'm taking you home!
What home?
You said...
You said... your wife...
Hey, don't...
Do not... talk about my wife!
You said...
That you could not do enough.
Now
now you
now you can.
I found a boat.
Don't go.
I will be right back.
A matter of hours.
But the baby, I don't know how...
I showed you how to do it.
Stay calm.
You have everything you need.
Everything.
Please...
I ook...
If I don't go...
Soon you'll be in a lot of pain.
And it won't know...
I won't lose you too.
Breathe...
Okay?
I'll be right back.
You make me happy
when skies are gray
you'll never know, dear
how much I love you
so please don't take my sunshine away
I'll be right back.
Hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hey. Look at me.
Hey.
Baby. Marcus.
Marcus! Marcus, wake up!
Thank you.
You heard the song.
You figured it out.
She did.
- I thought she was...
- Figured it out.
I'm not sure anyone here
can actually believe it.
I think most people had
finally given up hope.
Been a long time.
How long?
That day.
We got here the same way as you.
We were in the city
when we heard the hurricane sirens.
Once they knew they couldn't swim...
The national guard were told
to start loading people onto boats.
Any boat that they could find.
So as soon as people saw
the first one get out safe...
Well...
Everyone just started pushing forward.
And that's when they started screaming.
They had 12 boats
lined up on the dock that day.
Only two got out.
Anyway, you're here now.
A new day.
And where are you coming from?
Just over the appalachian Ridge.
And how long did it take?
Just under two days.
That's determination.
It's necessity.
To get help?
No.
To give it.
He said he'll do it.
Yes.
He said yes.
Thank you.
I wanted to say...
I'm sorry...
I doubted you.
I was wrong.
And you were right.
I'm nothing like him.
You are.
Get inside.
Get inside!
Stay down! Get down!
Hey, door's locked. You got a key?
Where is it?
We went too fast. What if we lost it?
Give me the key.
Jesus Christ, it went back!
- No, no, no.
- My family.
Alright. Listen to me.
I have to get back to my family.